Shido, what's in here?
Is it a date?
Tell me!
Upon Toka's arrival in this strange new world,
she was immediately faced with a challenge.
She could choose to fight against the appetite
of her growing curiosity,
or feed it generously with love.
And today, Shido's wallet is also feeling conflicted.
I can answer for more than 8 months later
The city knows it!
We might at all jump on some sort in the dark one
光求めた瞳
後ろは絶望だけ
誰にも届かない叫び
さあ ツその手で止めて
何もかも壊れた世界で
理由もわからないままに
増えた優しさがまだ
恐くて
花のあいた心の隙間 埋めてくれる人は君なの?
選んでD landslide
D sympathy
ın ad
D ko voilà
Thank you. Please come again.
Here you go.
Is this a test? Am I about to fail?
No, it's for you. Stop drooling.
Was this one of those date things?
No, it's bread.
Okay. Is that another name for date?
I don't understand how something so delicious can't be called a date.
You can call it one if you want to.
Fascinating. Even though this was delicious, it's still not good enough to be called a date.
And so the mystery continues.
There's one!
Not quite.
Oh, he's perfect. Where'd he come from?
Is this one?
In the case, I better attack before the Mecca Mecca squad.
No, wait. You don't want to do that.
Why are you stopping me? We're saving us!
I'm not. There's nothing to save us from. No one is trying to hurt us.
Look, Mama.
See? I threw it in the trash all by myself.
Oh, wow. What a good boy you are.
What about right now? This moment? Is this a date?
Not really, but you're getting closer.
Dates are complicated matters.
Look, that thing over there looks yummy!
How in the world are you still hungry?
Am I Kray or is that Shida with a new girl?
Oh my gosh, does that mean he's cheating on Tonomachi?
That's so lame.
That woman. I know she's a spirit.
But there's no spatial quake.
Sgt. Origami reporting.
A-0613. Need an observation device immediately.
No, racist!
I can't believe humans eat such amazingly delicious things!
Oh, hey, Toka.
What happened after you left yesterday?
Same thing as usual.
I swing my sword around some.
I blast the artillery.
In the end, my body disappeared naturally like it always does.
Disappeared?
Yes, I go to a world different from this one.
It's a dark space.
Once I get there, I just fall asleep.
So you mean when you wake up, you come here?
Well, I don't wake up on my own.
It's more like by force.
And it has nothing to do with what I want.
I'm just pulled here, usually anyway.
By force?
Then spirits don't cause spatial quakes on purpose.
They must just be accidents.
By usually, you mean today was different?
How would I know?
Please tell me.
Look, that might actually be the reason there wasn't a spatial quake today.
You're too persistent.
Besides, I have important things to do, like find more food.
Toka, come on.
Wait.
I should have brought more money.
It looks like she's a 98.5% match.
That's way too high to be a coincidence, of course.
But why is she here?
She isn't wearing her spirit armor right now.
If we want to attack, this is it.
Think about where you are.
You know we can't afford to be reckless.
What kind of place is this?
Uh, an expensive one.
I don't know what that means.
I'm going in.
No, wait, hold on.
Well, if it isn't Shido.
Momachi?
Hmm?
What do we have here?
That's some hot action.
How did you manage to pull that kind of tail without me knowing about it, huh?
I'm a little jealous.
Yeah, a lot has happened lately, I guess.
Whoa, and straight off the top of the shelf.
It's cool, man.
My lady's got some pretty expensive tastes, too.
Check it out.
Right.
His virtual girlfriend.
Listen, I want to help you.
Someone gave me these tickets, but I think they'll impress your fancy new girlie and help
you score later.
You're welcome in advance.
Let me know how it goes.
See you later, bud.
How are you today?
Reina?
What?
What are you doing here?
Checking on Princess.
We have to make sure we're not at risk of another spatial quake.
She's been waiting for you right over there.
Over here, Shido!
Why are you so late?
Sorry.
What's up, kitten?
You ready to order?
Kotari?
What?
I couldn't...
Hmm.
This looks so good, but so does that one.
I wonder which of these two is the date.
Hey, if you guys can't decide, I have a suggestion for you.
But how about this?
What does that one come with?
Whoa.
Should be called What's With All This?
How?
No, thank you.
It tastes so outrageous.
It must be a date.
What are you trying to pull here, Kotari?
Thank you works, too.
We're pulling out all the stops to help you score, because I'm awesome.
But we also have some business to discuss.
As soon as you guys leave, I need you to head south of the station.
But what for?
That's just a residential area.
Okay, then.
I trust you've got this.
Now, let's get this date started.
Checking AI analysis.
Use shop type E-5963.
E-5963.
Roger.
Open the main gate.
What's that?
Let's eat it!
It looks so yummy!
No, you can't eat them.
Well, you can, but not those.
Wow, they even have red ones.
They're so fast!
Yeah, the red ones are three times as fast as the others.
Don't know why they'd be here, though.
The heck is all that?
Congratulations!
What is going on here?
You two are this shopping arcade's 100,000 visitors!
So we have a special gift for both of you!
Everything you eat here today will be free!
Congratulations!
Thanks, but I don't get it.
I've never seen one of those before!
Wait, Toka, come back here!
Nice work, Kawagui.
All right.
Fried food team, get ready for service.
Fish cake and shaved ice team approach customers.
Noodle team, why was the delivery late?
Do you think we're going to be okay?
Shin and Toka are moving in.
Glad to see we're all ready and prepared for action.
Speak for yourself.
The signal's jammed.
Origami, can you hear me?
I've managed to squeeze mobilization orders from the higher-ups.
Meet us at point 101.
Roger that.
Yummy!
I can't get over the food!
What's that?
It looks amazing!
Ooh, so does this!
Jimmy!
Slow down!
Don't rush!
Eat as much as you want.
It's free.
How the hell did this happen?
Shito.
I'm having fun.
Are you?
Huh?
This has been such a great day, and I'm having a wonderful time here.
But I'm worried I'm the only one.
You seem upset.
Are you mad at me?
No way!
Of course I'm not mad at you!
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
In fact, I'm in a great mood.
I've just had a lot on my mind, is all.
Promise you're having a good time?
Best time ever.
I really hope you're telling the truth.
I am, I swear.
I'm glad we came here today.
There's so much food we have to try.
Let's get the most we can out of the state.
Yeah, let's.
Great, come on.
Okay.
Wherever you need me to go, I'll follow.
Congratulations, you two!
You won the grand prize!
Two tickets to Dream Park, redeemable any time!
Woo!
I don't know what that means, but it sounds like fun!
It's the most fun you'll ever have!
What's this?
You've never been?
That's unheard of!
You've got to take her right now!
Dream Park?
Game!
Go!
Whoa.
Look how beautiful this place is!
What an adventure!
What kind of things can we do in here?
Well, I don't know.
Do it, do it, do it!
Hey, I have an idea.
Let's not go in there, okay?
I don't agree.
You told me that we could go wherever I wanted today.
Shito, do you think I'll learn what a date is behind those doors?
Something tells me that's very possible.
But I don't think it's a good idea today.
Besides when I'm legal.
I'm not ready to go yet!
How am I supposed to learn if you won't let me experience these things?
Origami, where are you?
What's happening?
The time to meet has passed.
Currently surveying the movements of the target.
Send an emergency arming device to point 088107.
I can't believe I'm seeing this.
Why didn't he bring her in to do the deed?
This isn't the first time you've failed with that tactic, is it, Kawagale?
Fact established and acknowledged.
Classic Shito.
He always insists on doing everything in a proper order.
What's that?
Rain?
Strange.
There weren't any rain clouds in the vicinity.
Oh, well.
Maybe it's for the best.
Where did you bring me?
Is this the secret base of the Mecha Mecha Squad?
Of course not.
Don't worry.
Huh?
Why can't I get you, you unruly chicken?
Shito, tell this thing to cooperate.
I told you, this is a really tough one.
You have to have a strategy.
And yelling through the glass doesn't work.
Fine.
Then how?
This one should be easy.
It's sticking up.
That's not the one I want.
I want the chicken.
Okay.
Well, maybe there's another one like it somewhere.
I can get you whichever prize you want.
Come on.
Pick one.
Maybe that one.
I've got it.
Huh?
Listen closely.
I'll use this button over here.
You use the one on your side there.
Let go when I give the signal.
It's worth a shot.
Wait for it.
Now!
Let it go, Toka!
Chicken!
Hold on.
It still hasn't dropped yet.
I'm so sorry.
That was totally my fault.
I didn't give good instructions.
Drop the chicken!
Please drop it.
Why won't you listen to me?
Shito and I work so hard on this.
Drop it.
Please!
It's okay.
I'm begging you.
Drop it.
You have to!
Please!
We did it!
Question.
What method do those use to transform?
Actually, trains don't transform.
What?
So they use fusion?
Well, they do connect to each other.
Oh, wow!
Thank you.
I had so much fun today.
Good.
Me too.
Thanks for coming.
I am a little disappointed that we didn't get to explore Dream Park.
It's totally overrated.
If you say so.
But, Shito, the day is almost over and I still didn't see a date.
Can you tell me what one is like?
A date is just when a girl and a boy go out and have a good time together.
You can't actually see one.
Oh, that makes sense.
Well, in that case, I would say we had a wonderful date today.
Uh, sure.
I like dates.
They're nice.
Not good.
I can't believe I'm seeing this.
A spirit shows up without a spatial quake and then connects with a human boy.
Permission to shoot, miss?
Not yet.
Still waiting to hear from the top.
This is a very unusual situation.
No one's been evacuated.
I'll just have to wait and see.
Point Alpha here.
What happened?
What?
We've got permission to shoot?
All the humans were very kind today.
No one tried to kill you, did they?
I knew you'd be okay.
Yeah.
You're right.
I never knew the world was so kind.
So much fun.
And so beautiful.
I love it here.
And now, I understand why the Mecha Mecha Squad is after me.
Because whenever I appear in this world, something bad happens.
I ruin something beautiful.
I ruin your world.
That's not true.
So listen.
I've been thinking, and it's better if I don't exist anymore.
Don't say that.
We're fine.
There was no spatial quake today, was there?
You didn't ruin anything.
Yes, but that doesn't mean there won't be one the next time I appear.
However, once I go back and fall asleep, I won't be able to control myself.
Fine, then I guess you just can't go back.
Have you ever even tried?
Just once.
Just try staying here.
Even if I did, there are so many things I don't know about this world.
I'll teach you whatever you don't know.
Then I'd need food and then a place to sleep.
What if something happens we're not prepared for?
I'm going to take care of you.
If something comes up that we need to deal with, we'll deal with it.
Are you sure?
Am I even allowed to be here?
Is it okay for me to be alive in this world?
Yes, it is.
You're the only one who would say that to me.
Humans like the Mecha Mecha Squad, they don't want to risk it.
They don't want something as dangerous as me nearby.
I don't care about them.
Even if everyone else rejects you, it doesn't change the fact that I accept you and I don't want you to leave.
Take my hand.
That's the only job you have right now.
Distance, 512.15.
Wind direction, 40.8.
Wind speed, 0.4.
Temperature, 24 degrees.
RH, 52.8.
We're all clear.
Toka!
What are you doing?
Origami?
Origami, come in!
Origami!
Shiro.
I thought maybe if you were here for me, it would be okay.
It might be hard, but I'd be able to do it with you by my side.
I can get through anything when I'm with you.
But it doesn't matter.
It's no use. You're gone now.
I'm on my own.
This world has rejected me!
I don't know, I'm Eric!
I don't know.
How dare you?
How dare you reject me?
No way.
Origami, retreat immediately!
Support troops, where are you?
Origami, do you read me?
So it was you.
You're the one who did it.
You killed my only friend.
And with him, my soul, just admit it.
Yes, I killed Shido Itsuka.
Kill her.
She must pay for what she's done.
She must die.
It doesn't look like a pulse or heart rate is registering for Shido.
The special quick alarm is going off.
This can't be good.
Resident evacuation is still at 7%.
We're lucky there aren't many houses nearby.
But at this rate, the whole town will be decimated within minutes.
If she were a knight, she would have earned a passing brain.
But if she gets herself killed as a princess, then she's obviously not worth our concern.
Excuse me, Commander.
What have we heard about Shido?
Oh, I wouldn't worry too much about him.
My brother won't be finished off by something like that.
There it is.
Where am I?
Commander, what do we do now?
I already told you.
Even if Shido dies, he'll be able to start a new game.
So what the heck are you dragging ass for?
Get down there and recover him immediately.
No one else is able to stop her.
It has to be him.
That's right.
But the method we decided to save for last.
I did it.
I killed someone.
I'm like them.
The spirits.
They're the same.
We must end this.
Dad, Mom, I'm sorry.
Shido, I promise to avenge you.
Shido, is it really you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think it is.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming back.
You're crying.
Everything's okay now.
But...
Koka, what the heck is that?
I accidentally am she's helping to help.
I have to find someone to release it.
No, hold on.
You definitely can't do that.
Then what should I do?
It's already reached its critical state.
Shido, can you hear me?
Now is the time to use that method I taught you earlier.
It's the only way you'll be able to save her.
All right, Toka, listen to me.
We have to kiss now, okay?
We what?
Never mind.
Forget it.
I'm sorry.
There has to be another way.
No, I just don't know what a kiss is.
Teach me and I'll do it.
Um, okay, it's where we put our lips together
and then we...
I'm so sorry.
They told me this was the only way I could reverse it.
Just don't let me go.
I'm not ready for you to see me naked yet.
Shido.
Uh-huh?
Will you, um, take me out on another date sometime?
Of course.
Anytime you want to.
Huh?
Uh-huh.
See you next time.
Bye.